indiapages.com 2011-03-17

# Privacy Policy - IndiaPages.com

IndiaPages.com is committed to safeguarding your online privacy. The following policy acts as a guide in enabling you to understand how your personal information will be treated when you make use of the site. This policy may change from time to time.   

**What kind of personal information will be collected from you?**  
  
When you register on IndiaPages.com, personal data such as name, E-mail ID, address, phone number are required. On registration you will receive a unique user name that will give you complete access to IndiaPages.com In addition we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place ads or use other features of the IndiaPages.com   

**How is your information used?**  
  
IndiaPages.com collects your personal information to provide you with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout the IndiaPages.com  

**Who collects your information?**  
  
The personal information you furnish to IndiaPages.com will not be disclosed to anyone unless it is specifically stated otherwise. But some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users.   

**With whom your information may be shared?**  
  
IndiaPages.com will not disclose your personal information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances.  

IndiaPages.com may disclose account information only when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the IndiaPages.com or may be causing injury to or interference to its rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. IndiaPages.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.  

The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information Other than the administrator of the IndiaPages.com or other authorized personnel of IndiaPages.com you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access.  

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. IndiaPages.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited E-mail. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session in the IndiaPages.com This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.  

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, IndiaPages.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.  

**What else should you know about your online privacy?**  
  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
